NOW. >> SENATOR COREY BOOKER, THANK
>> SENATOR COREY BOOKER, THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US TONIGHT.
YOU FOR BEING WITH US TONIGHT. >> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME. >> THAT LAST POINT SENATOR
>> THAT LAST POINT SENATOR BOOKER WAS MAKING, THAT THIS
BOOKER WAS MAKING, THAT THIS NOMINEE WAS CHOSEN OFF A LIST,
NOMINEE WAS CHOSEN OFF A LIST, AN UNUSUAL THING.
AN UNUSUAL THING. THIS PRESIDENT SAID THAT HE
THIS PRESIDENT SAID THAT HE WOULD CHOOSE NOMINEES FROM A
WOULD CHOOSE NOMINEES FROM A LIST PREPARED BY CONSERVATIVE
LIST PREPARED BY CONSERVATIVE INTEREST GROUPS.
INTEREST GROUPS. HE IS SAYING THAT HE IS THE ONE
HE IS SAYING THAT HE IS THE ONE PERSON ON THAT LIST WHO IS
PERSON ON THAT LIST WHO IS EXPLICITLY ON THE RECORD TALKING
EXPLICITLY ON THE RECORD TALKING ABOUT A PRESIDENT’S LIABILITY TO
ABOUT A PRESIDENT’S LIABILITY TO CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION AND
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION AND INDICTMENT.
INDICTMENT. AND SAYING, AS SENATOR BOOKER.
AND SAYING, AS SENATOR BOOKER. THAT A PRESIDENT SHOULD NOT BE
THAT A PRESIDENT SHOULD NOT BE SUBL TO CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
SUBL TO CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION AND CANNOT BE INDICTED.
AND CANNOT BE INDICTED. IF HE IS THE ONE GUY FROM THAT
IF HE IS THE ONE GUY FROM THAT LIST OF 2000 CHOICES WHO HAS
LIST OF 2000 CHOICES WHO HAS BEEN EXPLICIT ON THAT POINT, IS
BEEN EXPLICIT ON THAT POINT, IS THAT THE SIGNAL ELEMENT THAT WE
THAT THE SIGNAL ELEMENT THAT WE SHOULD SEE HERE IN THIS CHOICE?
SHOULD SEE HERE IN THIS CHOICE? JOINING US ONCE AGAIN, LEGAL
JOINING US ONCE AGAIN, LEGAL CORRESPONDENT AT SLATE.COM.
CORRESPONDENT AT SLATE.COM. TO THIS POINT IS SENATOR BOOKER
TO THIS POINT IS SENATOR BOOKER CORRECT THAT KAVANAUGH HAS AN
CORRECT THAT KAVANAUGH HAS AN AND MISSION IT OVERT RECORD THAT
AND MISSION IT OVERT RECORD THAT MIGHT APPEAL TO THE PRESIDENT
MIGHT APPEAL TO THE PRESIDENT BECAUSE OF HIS OWN LEGAL WOES?
BECAUSE OF HIS OWN LEGAL WOES? >> I THINK IF THE PRESIDENT WERE
>> I THINK IF THE PRESIDENT WERE POURING OVER THE WRITINGS OF
POURING OVER THE WRITINGS OF EVERY PERSON ON THE LIST, JUDGE
EVERY PERSON ON THE LIST, JUDGE KAVANAUGH WOULD HAVE GIVEN HIM
KAVANAUGH WOULD HAVE GIVEN HIM MOST SUCKER.
MOST SUCKER. I WANT TO CLARIFY ONE THING.
I WANT TO CLARIFY ONE THING. IN THE ARTICLE WHERE HE TALKED
IN THE ARTICLE WHERE HE TALKED ABOUT THIS, HE DIDN’T SAY AS A
ABOUT THIS, HE DIDN’T SAY AS A CONSTITUTIONAL MATTER THE
CONSTITUTIONAL MATTER THE PRESIDENT SHOULD BE IMMUNE FROM
PRESIDENT SHOULD BE IMMUNE FROM ALL CIVIL AND LIABILITY.
ALL CIVIL AND LIABILITY. HE SAID CONGRESS SHOULD PASS A
HE SAID CONGRESS SHOULD PASS A LAW TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT.
LAW TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT. I DON’T THINK HE WAS MAKING THE
I DON’T THINK HE WAS MAKING THE CONSTITUTIONAL POINT THAT IS
CONSTITUTIONAL POINT THAT IS QUITE SO BROAD.
QUITE SO BROAD. >> HE’S MAKING A MILL ARGUMENT
>> HE’S MAKING A MILL ARGUMENT THAT THE IMPEACHMENT OF A
THAT THE IMPEACHMENT OF A PRESIDENT WOULD PUT A PROSECUTOR
PRESIDENT WOULD PUT A PROSECUTOR IN THE PLACE OF SUPPLANTING
IN THE PLACE OF SUPPLANTING CONGRESS’ RESPONSIBILITY TO
CONGRESS’ RESPONSIBILITY TO IMPEACH.
IMPEACH. >> I THINK IT IS IMPORTANT
>> I THINK IT IS IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT IS NOT QUITE AS
BECAUSE IT IS NOT QUITE AS DISPOSITIVE OF THIS QUESTION AS
DISPOSITIVE OF THIS QUESTION AS WE WOULD LIKE TO THINK.
WE WOULD LIKE TO THINK. ON YOUR QUESTION, IF YOU THINK
ON YOUR QUESTION, IF YOU THINK ABOUT HOW MUCH FIRE KAVANAUGH
ABOUT HOW MUCH FIRE KAVANAUGH DREW.
DREW. TED CRUZ HATED HIM.
TED CRUZ HATED HIM. WE HAD THEM SAYING, WE WON’T BE
WE HAD THEM SAYING, WE WON’T BE FOR TRUMP IF HE PUTS KAVANAUGH
FOR TRUMP IF HE PUTS KAVANAUGH UP.
UP. WHAT WAS THE RESISTANCE TO
WHAT WAS THE RESISTANCE TO KAVANAUGH?
KAVANAUGH? IT HAS BEEN REALLY INTERESTING
IT HAS BEEN REALLY INTERESTING TO ME.
TO ME. I THOUGHT FOR A LONG TIME IT WAS
I THOUGHT FOR A LONG TIME IT WAS JUST THAT HE WASN’T A SORT OF
JUST THAT HE WASN’T A SORT OF RELIGIOUS CONSERVATIVE.
RELIGIOUS CONSERVATIVE. THIS WASN’T GOING TO BE THE
THIS WASN’T GOING TO BE THE FIREFIGHT THAT SOME OF THE
FIREFIGHT THAT SOME OF THE EVANGELICAL COMMUNITY WANTED.
EVANGELICAL COMMUNITY WANTED. TED CRUZ HAS BEEN WARNING THAT
TED CRUZ HAS BEEN WARNING THAT HE’S GOING TO BE A SUITOR.
HE’S GOING TO BE A SUITOR. >> ARE THERE ANY INDICATIONS, HE
>> ARE THERE ANY INDICATIONS, HE HAS MORE THAN 300 OPINIONS.
HAS MORE THAN 300 OPINIONS. HE’S BEEN ON THE APPEALS COURT
HE’S BEEN ON THE APPEALS COURT FOR A DOZEN YEARS.
FOR A DOZEN YEARS. VERY IDEOLOGICALLY CHARGED.
VERY IDEOLOGICALLY CHARGED. HE WAS BUSH-GORE RECOUNT LAWYER.
HE WAS BUSH-GORE RECOUNT LAWYER. A GEORGE W. BUSH WHITE HOUSE
A GEORGE W. BUSH WHITE HOUSE EMPLOYEE FOR MORE THAN FOUR
EMPLOYEE FOR MORE THAN FOUR YEARS.
YEARS. WHAT WOULD ALLOW CONSERVATIVE
WHAT WOULD ALLOW CONSERVATIVE CRITICS TO SEE HIM THAT WAY?
CRITICS TO SEE HIM THAT WAY? >> I HAVE NO IDEA BUT I WAS
>> I HAVE NO IDEA BUT I WAS STUNNED WITH HOW THEY CAME OUT
STUNNED WITH HOW THEY CAME OUT AGAINST HIM AND I THINK THAT
AGAINST HIM AND I THINK THAT DONALD TRUMP WAS MAKING EXACTLY
DONALD TRUMP WAS MAKING EXACTLY THE CALCULUS YOU JUST
THE CALCULUS YOU JUST IDENTIFIED.
IDENTIFIED. IF I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO TO
IF I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHO TO MOLLIFY, I HAVE ALL THESE GROUPS
MOLLIFY, I HAVE ALL THESE GROUPS ANGRY ABOUT SOMEONE.
ANGRY ABOUT SOMEONE. I AM GOING TO PROTECT MYSELF.
I AM GOING TO PROTECT MYSELF. I AM GOING TO FICK GUY WHO WROTE
I AM GOING TO FICK GUY WHO WROTE MOST EXPANSIVELY OVER YEARS WHAT
MOST EXPANSIVELY OVER YEARS WHAT THE SCOPE OF PRESIDENTIAL POWER
THE SCOPE OF PRESIDENTIAL POWER IS.
IS. IN THAT SENSE YOU SEE TRUMP NOT
IN THAT SENSE YOU SEE TRUMP NOT LOOKING AT THE LANDSCAPE OF
LOOKING AT THE LANDSCAPE OF THAT.
THAT. >> LET’S JUST QUOTE DIRECTLY
>> LET’S JUST QUOTE DIRECTLY JUDGE KAVANAUGH FROM A 1998
JUDGE KAVANAUGH FROM A 1998 GEORGETOWN LAW ARTICLE.
GEORGETOWN LAW ARTICLE. QUOTE, CONGRESS SHOULD
QUOTE, CONGRESS SHOULD ESTABLISH, IMPORTANT TO POINT
ESTABLISH, IMPORTANT TO POINT THAT OUT, CONGRESS SHOULD
THAT OUT, CONGRESS SHOULD ESTABLISH THAT THE PRESIDENT CAN
ESTABLISH THAT THE PRESIDENT CAN BE INDICTED ONLY AFTER LEAVES
BE INDICTED ONLY AFTER LEAVES OFFICE VOLUNTARILY OR IS
OFFICE VOLUNTARILY OR IS IMPEACHED BY THE HOUSE AND
IMPEACHED BY THE HOUSE AND CONVICTED AND REMOVED BY THE
CONVICTED AND REMOVED BY THE SENATE.
SENATE. THAT’S KAVANAUGH ON THE RECORD
THAT’S KAVANAUGH ON THE RECORD SAYING, THERE SHOULD BE NO
SAYING, THERE SHOULD BE NO INDICTMENT OF A SITTING