BATTLE FOR OUR BETTER ANGELS" WHICH WE APPEAR TO BE IN TODAY,
WHICH WE APPEAR TO BE IN TODAY, JON MEACHUM.
JON MEACHUM. GOOD TO HAVE YOU ALL ON BOARD.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU ALL ON BOARD. THIS IS WHERE WE BEGIN.
THIS IS WHERE WE BEGIN. WITH LIES, STRAIGHT ON DOWN FROM
WITH LIES, STRAIGHT ON DOWN FROM THE TOP.
THE TOP. PRESIDENT TRUMP’S LAWYER, RUDY
PRESIDENT TRUMP’S LAWYER, RUDY GIULIANI, IS CALLING ON THE
GIULIANI, IS CALLING ON THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TO
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TO IMMEDIATELY SUSPEND SPECIAL
IMMEDIATELY SUSPEND SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER’S PROBE.
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER’S PROBE. AND TO LAUNCH AN INVESTIGATION
AND TO LAUNCH AN INVESTIGATION OF THE INVESTIGATORS.
OF THE INVESTIGATORS. GIULIANI’S STATEMENT CAME AFTER
GIULIANI’S STATEMENT CAME AFTER YESTERDAY’S UNUSUAL SILENCE FROM
YESTERDAY’S UNUSUAL SILENCE FROM THE PRESIDENT ABOUT THE DOJ’S
THE PRESIDENT ABOUT THE DOJ’S INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT ON THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT ON THE FBI’S INVESTIGATION OF 2016
FBI’S INVESTIGATION OF 2016 PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES.
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES. THE NEWS GETS STAGGERING THIS
THE NEWS GETS STAGGERING THIS MORNING WHEN WE STARTED WITH
MORNING WHEN WE STARTED WITH SARAH SANDERS AND HERE WE ARE
SARAH SANDERS AND HERE WE ARE NOW.
NOW. HOURS BEFORE EX-TRUMP CAMPAIGN
HOURS BEFORE EX-TRUMP CAMPAIGN MANAGER PAUL MANAFORT HEADS TO
MANAGER PAUL MANAFORT HEADS TO COURT THIS MORNING FOR A BAIL
COURT THIS MORNING FOR A BAIL HEARING OVER WITNESS TAMPERING
HEARING OVER WITNESS TAMPERING CLAIMS, HE PLEESDS NOT GUILTY TO
CLAIMS, HE PLEESDS NOT GUILTY TO CHARGES, INCLUDING FRAUD AND
CHARGES, INCLUDING FRAUD AND MONEY LAUNDERING.
MONEY LAUNDERING. GIULIANI INSISTED HE WAS
GIULIANI INSISTED HE WAS SPEAKING FOR HIMSELF BUT HIS
SPEAKING FOR HIMSELF BUT HIS DEMAND COINCIDED WITH OTHER
DEMAND COINCIDED WITH OTHER TRUMP ALLIES, CLAIMING THE
TRUMP ALLIES, CLAIMING THE REPORT HAD BEARING ON MUELLER’S
REPORT HAD BEARING ON MUELLER’S LEGITIMACY.
LEGITIMACY. EVEN THOUGH MUELLER REMOVED
EVEN THOUGH MUELLER REMOVED AGENT PETER STRZOK LAST SUMMER
AGENT PETER STRZOK LAST SUMMER WHEN HE LEARNED OF ANTI-TRUMP
WHEN HE LEARNED OF ANTI-TRUMP TEXT MESSAGES TO STRZOK’S LOVER,
TEXT MESSAGES TO STRZOK’S LOVER, FBI ATTORNEY LISA PAGE.
FBI ATTORNEY LISA PAGE. >> WE SUPPLY EDIED 1.4 MILLION
>> WE SUPPLY EDIED 1.4 MILLION DOCUMENTS.
DOCUMENTS. AGENTS WHO STARTED A PHONY
AGENTS WHO STARTED A PHONY RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION. THAT’S THE WHOLE CORE OF THIS.
THAT’S THE WHOLE CORE OF THIS. THAT’S WHY THE INVESTIGATION
THAT’S WHY THE INVESTIGATION SHOULD BE SUSPENDED.
SHOULD BE SUSPENDED. AND I’M TALKING FOR MYSELF, NOT
AND I’M TALKING FOR MYSELF, NOT THE PRESIDENT, BUT I BELIEVE HE
THE PRESIDENT, BUT I BELIEVE HE WOULD AGREE WITH THIS.
WOULD AGREE WITH THIS. VERY SERIOUS INVESTIGATION HAS
VERY SERIOUS INVESTIGATION HAS TO BE DONE OF THE FBI AGENTS AT
TO BE DONE OF THE FBI AGENTS AT THE VERY TOP.
THE VERY TOP. BY FBI AGENTS WHO ARE HONEST.
BY FBI AGENTS WHO ARE HONEST. IN ORDER TO PROSECUTE --
IN ORDER TO PROSECUTE -- PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SAID OVER
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SAID OVER AND OVER AGAIN TO ME, I DID
AND OVER AGAIN TO ME, I DID NOTHING WRONG.
NOTHING WRONG. HOW COULD THIS BE?
HOW COULD THIS BE? NOW WE KNOW HOW IT IS.
NOW WE KNOW HOW IT IS. BECAUSE THESE PEOPLE FIXED IT.
BECAUSE THESE PEOPLE FIXED IT. THAT’S HOW IT IS.
THAT’S HOW IT IS. READ THIS, IF YOU’RE NOT
READ THIS, IF YOU’RE NOT DISGUSTED, AND YOU DON’T DEMAND
DISGUSTED, AND YOU DON’T DEMAND THAT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
THAT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT BEGIN THIS INVESTIGATION, AND
BEGIN THIS INVESTIGATION, AND SUSPEND THE ONE OF THE PRESIDENT
SUSPEND THE ONE OF THE PRESIDENT AND ALL THE PEOPLE THAT HAVE
AND ALL THE PEOPLE THAT HAVE BEEN TORTURED BY IT.
BEEN TORTURED BY IT. I BELIEVE THAT ROD ROSENSTEIN
I BELIEVE THAT ROD ROSENSTEIN AND JEFF SESSIONS HAVE A CHANCE
AND JEFF SESSIONS HAVE A CHANCE TO REDEEM THEMSELVES AND THAT
TO REDEEM THEMSELVES AND THAT CHANCE COMES ABOUT TOMORROW IT
CHANCE COMES ABOUT TOMORROW IT DOESN’T GO BEYOND TOMORROW.
DOESN’T GO BEYOND TOMORROW. TOMORROW, MUELLER SHOULD BE
TOMORROW, MUELLER SHOULD BE SUSPENDED AND HONEST PEOPLE
SUSPENDED AND HONEST PEOPLE SHOULD BE BROUGHT IN, IMPARTIAL
SHOULD BE BROUGHT IN, IMPARTIAL PEOPLE TO INVESTIGATE THESE
PEOPLE TO INVESTIGATE THESE PEOPLE LIKE STRZOK.
PEOPLE LIKE STRZOK. STRZOK SHOULD BE IN JAIL BY THE
STRZOK SHOULD BE IN JAIL BY THE END OF NEXT WEEK.
END OF NEXT WEEK. >> RUDY GIULIANI, I MEAN RUDY
>> RUDY GIULIANI, I MEAN RUDY GIULIANI IS SHAMING HIMSELF AS
GIULIANI IS SHAMING HIMSELF AS USUAL.
USUAL. RUDY GIULIANI IS MAKING A FOOL
RUDY GIULIANI IS MAKING A FOOL OF HIMSELF.
OF HIMSELF. RUDY GIULIANI IS LYING TO THE
RUDY GIULIANI IS LYING TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
AMERICAN PEOPLE. RUDY GIULIANI IS, IS TRASHING
RUDY GIULIANI IS, IS TRASHING THE ENTIRE FBI BECAUSE OF A
THE ENTIRE FBI BECAUSE OF A COUPLE OF FBI AGENTS WHO WERE
COUPLE OF FBI AGENTS WHO WERE FIRED LAST YEAR.
FIRED LAST YEAR. RUDY GIULIANI IS NO FOOL.
RUDY GIULIANI IS NO FOOL. THOUGH HE PLAYS ONE ON
THOUGH HE PLAYS ONE ON TELEVISION.
TELEVISION. HE KNOWS THAT FBI AGENTS ALSO
HE KNOWS THAT FBI AGENTS ALSO DURING THE CAMPAIGN WERE
DURING THE CAMPAIGN WERE TRASHING HILLARY CLINTON IN NEW
TRASHING HILLARY CLINTON IN NEW YORK.
YORK. IT WAS A COMMON OCCURRENCE.
IT WAS A COMMON OCCURRENCE. RUDY GIULIANI, UNLESS HE’S A
RUDY GIULIANI, UNLESS HE’S A FOOL ALSO KNOWS THAT WHILE
FOOL ALSO KNOWS THAT WHILE BARACK OBAMA WAS PRESIDENT OF
BARACK OBAMA WAS PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES, C.I.A. AGENTS
THE UNITED STATES, C.I.A. AGENTS REGULARLY TRASHED BARACK OBAMA.
REGULARLY TRASHED BARACK OBAMA. I KNOW BECAUSE THEY TRASHED
I KNOW BECAUSE THEY TRASHED BARACK OBAMA TO ME.
BARACK OBAMA TO ME. FBI AGENTS DID THE SAME.
FBI AGENTS DID THE SAME. GUESS WHAT, DURING THE BUILD-UP
GUESS WHAT, DURING THE BUILD-UP TO THE GULF WAR YOU KNOW WHO THE
TO THE GULF WAR YOU KNOW WHO THE C.I.A. AGENTS AND FBI AGENTS
C.I.A. AGENTS AND FBI AGENTS TRASHED?
TRASHED? GEORGE W. BUSH.
GEORGE W. BUSH. YOU ARE ALL ARE ACTING LIKE SUCH
YOU ARE ALL ARE ACTING LIKE SUCH SNOWFLAKES IT’S AS IF THE PRIME
SNOWFLAKES IT’S AS IF THE PRIME MINISTER OF CANADA SAID
MINISTER OF CANADA SAID SOMETHING MEAN TO YOU, YOU’RE
SOMETHING MEAN TO YOU, YOU’RE ASKING LIKE IT’S THE FIRST TIME
ASKING LIKE IT’S THE FIRST TIME IT’S EVER HAPPENED.
IT’S EVER HAPPENED. A PHONY INVESTIGATION?
A PHONY INVESTIGATION? LET ME HOLD UP LOTS OF PAPERS,
LET ME HOLD UP LOTS OF PAPERS, RUDY THIMPGS YOU’RE TOO STUPID
RUDY THIMPGS YOU’RE TOO STUPID TO NOT BE LIKE BROUGHT INTO THIS
TO NOT BE LIKE BROUGHT INTO THIS TIZZY, BECAUSE HE HOLDS UP LOTS
TIZZY, BECAUSE HE HOLDS UP LOTS OF PAPERS.
OF PAPERS. IF YOU READ THIS.
IF YOU READ THIS. BECAUSE I’VE WRIT TN DOWN HERE.
BECAUSE I’VE WRIT TN DOWN HERE. YOU’LL FIND OUT THAT THEY’VE
YOU’LL FIND OUT THAT THEY’VE ALREADY IN THIS PHONY
ALREADY IN THIS PHONY INVESTIGATION OF RUDY GIULIANI,
INVESTIGATION OF RUDY GIULIANI, HAVE ALREADY BEEN 13 RUSSIANS
HAVE ALREADY BEEN 13 RUSSIANS INDICTED.
INDICTED. THAT’S A HELL OF A PHONY
THAT’S A HELL OF A PHONY INVESTIGATION.
INVESTIGATION. 13 INDICTED BY AMERICANS IN A
13 INDICTED BY AMERICANS IN A GRAND JURY OVERSEEN BY AN
GRAND JURY OVERSEEN BY AN AMERICAN JUDGE.
AMERICAN JUDGE. 13 RUSSIANS INDICTED.
13 RUSSIANS INDICTED. OH, AN ADDITIONAL RUSSIAN
OH, AN ADDITIONAL RUSSIAN INDICTED.
INDICTED. OH, WAIT, HOLD ON A SECOND, THIS
OH, WAIT, HOLD ON A SECOND, THIS INFORMATION THAT I’M READING
INFORMATION THAT I’M READING HERE THAT YOU SHOULD BE BLOWN
HERE THAT YOU SHOULD BE BLOWN AWAY BY ALSO SHOWS THAT THE MAN
AWAY BY ALSO SHOWS THAT THE MAN THAT RAN DONALD TRUMP’S NATIONAL
THAT RAN DONALD TRUMP’S NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY, INDICTED.
SECURITY AGENCY, INDICTED. PLED GUILTY IN THIS PHONY
PLED GUILTY IN THIS PHONY INVESTIGATION AND IS NOW
INVESTIGATION AND IS NOW COOPERATING WITH FEDERAL
COOPERATING WITH FEDERAL AUTHORITIES.
AUTHORITIES. BUT WAIT.
BUT WAIT. THERE’S MORE.
THERE’S MORE. THE MAN THAT DONALD TRUMP SAID
THE MAN THAT DONALD TRUMP SAID WAS RUNNING HIS NATURAL SECURITY
WAS RUNNING HIS NATURAL SECURITY TEAM.
TEAM. HEAD OF FOREIGN POLICY.
HEAD OF FOREIGN POLICY. GEORGE PAPADOPOULOS HE TOLD THE
GEORGE PAPADOPOULOS HE TOLD THE "WASHINGTON POST," INDICTED,
"WASHINGTON POST," INDICTED, PLED GUILTY AND IS NOW
PLED GUILTY AND IS NOW COOPERATING WITH FEDS.
COOPERATING WITH FEDS. BOY, THAT’S SOME PHONY
BOY, THAT’S SOME PHONY INVESTIGATION.
INVESTIGATION. BUT WAIT, THERE’S MORE.
BUT WAIT, THERE’S MORE. ONE OF DONALD TRUMP’S TOP
ONE OF DONALD TRUMP’S TOP CAMPAIGN MANAGERS DURING THE
CAMPAIGN MANAGERS DURING THE 2016 CAMPAIGN HAS PLED GUILTY.
2016 CAMPAIGN HAS PLED GUILTY. AND IS NOW COOPERATING WITH
AND IS NOW COOPERATING WITH AUTHORITIES.
AUTHORITIES. WHY, THAT’S SOME FUNNY WITCH
WHY, THAT’S SOME FUNNY WITCH HUNT.
HUNT. OH, WAIT, THERE’S MORE.
OH, WAIT, THERE’S MORE. PAUL MANAFORT, THE MAN WHO IS
PAUL MANAFORT, THE MAN WHO IS RUNNING THE CAMPAIGN, JON
RUNNING THE CAMPAIGN, JON HEILEMANN, THE MAN WHO DONALD
HEILEMANN, THE MAN WHO DONALD TRUMP SAID HE HAD TO GET ON
TRUMP SAID HE HAD TO GET ON BOARD, SO HE COULD WIN THE
BOARD, SO HE COULD WIN THE REPUBLICAN NOMINATION, IS GOING
REPUBLICAN NOMINATION, IS GOING BACK INTO COURT TODAY, HE’S BEEN
BACK INTO COURT TODAY, HE’S BEEN INDICTED BY A GRAND JURY OF
INDICTED BY A GRAND JURY OF AMERICANS, OF AMERICANS, WITH AN
AMERICANS, OF AMERICANS, WITH AN AMERICAN JUDGE, LISTENING IN,
AMERICAN JUDGE, LISTENING IN, BEEN INDICTED AND MAN FFRT IS
BEEN INDICTED AND MAN FFRT IS GOING TO GO TO JAIL TODAY.
GOING TO GO TO JAIL TODAY. NOW I DON’T KNOW WHO IS STUPID
NOW I DON’T KNOW WHO IS STUPID ENOUGH TO LISTEN TO RUDY
ENOUGH TO LISTEN TO RUDY GIULIANI AND BELIEVE RUDY
GIULIANI AND BELIEVE RUDY GIULIANI.
GIULIANI. BUT I’M ASKING, IF YOU ARE
BUT I’M ASKING, IF YOU ARE STUPID ENOUGH TO BELIEVE THAT,
STUPID ENOUGH TO BELIEVE THAT, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THEN I’M
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THEN I’M GOING TO ASK MY JUDGE TO GET
GOING TO ASK MY JUDGE TO GET YOUR PHONE NUMBER AND CAST YOU
YOUR PHONE NUMBER AND CAST YOU IN I HAD OKAYCY CYIDIOCRACY II.
IN I HAD OKAYCY CYIDIOCRACY II. BECAUSE I DON’T BELIEVE THERE’S
BECAUSE I DON’T BELIEVE THERE’S ANYONE THAT STUPID.
ANYONE THAT STUPID. >> WELL UNFORTUNATELY, WHETHER
>> WELL UNFORTUNATELY, WHETHER YOU CALL THEM STUPID OR NOT,
YOU CALL THEM STUPID OR NOT, THIS --
THIS -- >> YOU HAVE TO BE STUPID WITH 20
>> YOU HAVE TO BE STUPID WITH 20 INDICTMENTS BY AMERICANS --
INDICTMENTS BY AMERICANS -- >> DUDE, I’M WITH YOU.
>> DUDE, I’M WITH YOU. >> BY AMERICAN GRAND JURIES, YOU
>> BY AMERICAN GRAND JURIES, YOU HAVE TO BE STUPID AND ALSO I’M
HAVE TO BE STUPID AND ALSO I’M SORRY, BUT DIDN’T THE FBI HELP
SORRY, BUT DIDN’T THE FBI HELP ELECT DONALD TRUMP?
ELECT DONALD TRUMP? THAT’S, YOU KNOW I THINK THAT’S
THAT’S, YOU KNOW I THINK THAT’S THE MOST FRUSTRATING THING.
THE MOST FRUSTRATING THING. THAT THE VERY, THE VERY BREACH
THAT THE VERY, THE VERY BREACH OF PROTOCOL OF JAMES COMEY, HAD
OF PROTOCOL OF JAMES COMEY, HAD HIM SEND OUT A LETTER, TEN DAYS
HIM SEND OUT A LETTER, TEN DAYS BEFORE, WHEN THE FBI WAS SITTING
BEFORE, WHEN THE FBI WAS SITTING ON THAT INFORMATION FOR 20 DAYS
ON THAT INFORMATION FOR 20 DAYS AND HELPED ELECT DONALD TRUMP.
AND HELPED ELECT DONALD TRUMP. >> THERE’S NO DOUBT THERE’S AN
>> THERE’S NO DOUBT THERE’S AN AUDIENCE OUT THERE OF AMERICANS,
AUDIENCE OUT THERE OF AMERICANS, OTHER AMERICAN WHO IS FIND RUDY
OTHER AMERICAN WHO IS FIND RUDY GIULIANI’S ARGUMENTS PERSUASIVE.
GIULIANI’S ARGUMENTS PERSUASIVE. THERE ARE.
THERE ARE. WE’VE SEEN IT IN THE POLLING.
WE’VE SEEN IT IN THE POLLING. THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE OUT
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE OUT THERE -- GO THEN THEY’RE
THERE -- GO THEN THEY’RE IGNORANT OF THE FACTS.
IGNORANT OF THE FACTS. >> I’M NOT STICKING UP FOR THEM,
>> I’M NOT STICKING UP FOR THEM, I’M MAKING A POINT THERE’S NO
I’M MAKING A POINT THERE’S NO DOUBT THE ARGUMENT.
DOUBT THE ARGUMENT. THIS WAS THE MOST, THE WAY THAT
THIS WAS THE MOST, THE WAY THAT GIULIANI HAS REACTED.
GIULIANI HAS REACTED. THE WAY THAT THE ADMINISTRATION
THE WAY THAT THE ADMINISTRATION HAS REACTED AND THE WAY THAT
HAS REACTED AND THE WAY THAT DONALD TRUMP WILL REACT, IN THE
DONALD TRUMP WILL REACT, IN THE COURSE OF THE NEXT 24 HOURS OR
COURSE OF THE NEXT 24 HOURS OR SOONER, ALL OF THIS, THE
SOONER, ALL OF THIS, THE REACTION TO THE REPORT WAS
REACTION TO THE REPORT WAS TOTALLY PREDICTABLE.
TOTALLY PREDICTABLE. >> DON’T THE PRESS HAVE A
>> DON’T THE PRESS HAVE A RESPONSIBILITY --
RESPONSIBILITY -- >> IT DOES.
>> IT DOES. >> I HAD TO SIFT THROUGH REPORTS
>> I HAD TO SIFT THROUGH REPORTS YESTERDAY UNTIL I GOT TO THE
YESTERDAY UNTIL I GOT TO THE POINT WHERE THE IG SAID, THE IG
POINT WHERE THE IG SAID, THE IG FOUND OUT THAT COMEY HELD THE
FOUND OUT THAT COMEY HELD THE INFORMATION A MONTH LONGER THAN
INFORMATION A MONTH LONGER THAN HE SHOULD HAVE.
HE SHOULD HAVE. WHICH ELECTED DONALD TRUMP.
WHICH ELECTED DONALD TRUMP. >> THE BIGGEST TAKE-AWAYS FROM
>> THE BIGGEST TAKE-AWAYS FROM THIS REPORT.
THIS REPORT. THE BIGGEST ONES OUT OF 500
THE BIGGEST ONES OUT OF 500 PAGES, THE BIGGEST TAKE-AWAYS
PAGES, THE BIGGEST TAKE-AWAYS ARE, THERE IS ONE TEXT MESSAGE
ARE, THERE IS ONE TEXT MESSAGE FROM PETER STRZOK THAT WE DID
FROM PETER STRZOK THAT WE DID NOT KNOW ABOUT THAT DONALD TRUMP
NOT KNOW ABOUT THAT DONALD TRUMP AND HIS ALLIES ARE GOING TO
AND HIS ALLIES ARE GOING TO SEIZE ON AND TALK ABOUT ALL DAY
SEIZE ON AND TALK ABOUT ALL DAY LONG TODAY IN WHICH STRZOK SAID
LONG TODAY IN WHICH STRZOK SAID IN SOME TONE THAT WE CAN’T TELL
IN SOME TONE THAT WE CAN’T TELL EITHER WITH THE TONE OF INTENT
EITHER WITH THE TONE OF INTENT AND SERIOUSNESS, OR A THROW-AWAY
AND SERIOUSNESS, OR A THROW-AWAY LINE.
LINE. WHO KNOWS.
WHO KNOWS. >> LET ME ASK YOU THIS -- LET ME
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS -- LET ME ASK YOU THIS, THIS IS FOR THE
ASK YOU THIS, THIS IS FOR THE STUPID PEOPLE, WHO ACTUALLY
STUPID PEOPLE, WHO ACTUALLY BELIEVE THIS.
BELIEVE THIS. I GOT TO SAY SOME OF YOU PEOPLE
I GOT TO SAY SOME OF YOU PEOPLE TWEETING YESTERDAY -- STOP
TWEETING YESTERDAY -- STOP SHAMING YOURSELF.
SHAMING YOURSELF. JUST STOP SHAMING YOURSELF.
JUST STOP SHAMING YOURSELF. YOU’RE EMBARRASSING YOURSELF
YOU’RE EMBARRASSING YOURSELF BECAUSE THE BOTTOM LINE OF THIS